<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://abbymanock.com/wordle-spoiler-podcast/1</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2026 Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2</url>
      <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
      <link>https://abbymanock.com/wordle-spoiler-podcast/1</link>
    </image>
    <itunes:subtitle>A podcast about spelling, language, and games</itunes:subtitle>
    <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
    <itunes:summary>WORDLE SPOILER is a recap, review and in-depth analysis of the daily Wordle experience. WARNING: Do not listen to this podcast if you haven't done your Wordle yet today! WE WILL SPOIL IT!</itunes:summary>
    <description>WORDLE SPOILER is a recap, review and in-depth analysis of the daily Wordle experience. WARNING: Do not listen to this podcast if you haven't done your Wordle yet today! WE WILL SPOIL IT!</description>
    <itunes:owner>
      <itunes:name>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:name>
      <itunes:email>wordlespoilerpodcast@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
    <itunes:category text="Games &amp; Hobbies">
      <itunes:category text="Video Games"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:category text="Education">
      <itunes:category text="Language Learning"/>
    </itunes:category>
    <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
CCaseyPro planFree RSS feed publishing optionsCan I use this for free? Can I publish an RSS feed for free or do I need to be a member?Jan 19I'd be happy to help clarify what you can do for free! However, I need a bit more context - are you asking about:

Claude.ai (this chat interface) - whether you can use it for free and if there are limitations?
A specific service or platform for publishing RSS feeds that we were discussing?
Something else entirely?

If you're asking about Claude.ai specifically, yes, there is a free tier available that lets you have conversations with me. However, the free tier does have some limitations compared to paid plans (like message limits and access to certain features). For the most current details about what's included in the free tier versus paid plans, I should search Anthropic's documentation to give you accurate information.
If you're asking about publishing RSS feeds through a different service or platform, please let me know which one and I can help you find that information!I want to make a rss feed for a podcast, do I need to pay for it?Jan 19No, you don't need to pay to create an RSS feed for a podcast! Here's what you should know:
Free options:

You can create an RSS feed completely for free using various podcast hosting platforms that offer free tiers, such as Anchor (now Spotify for Podcasters), Buzzsprout's free plan, or Podbean's free plan
You can also manually create your own RSS feed if you have a website - it's just an XML file that follows the podcast RSS specification
If you host your audio files on your own server or free cloud storage, you can generate the RSS feed yourself at no cost

What typically costs money:

Hosting your audio files - while some platforms offer limited free hosting, you may eventually need to pay for bandwidth/storage as your podcast grows
Advanced features - analytics, multiple shows, removing platform branding, more upload hours per month
Distribution help - some paid services make it easier to submit to directories like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, etc. (though you can do this yourself for free)

My recommendation: Start with a free podcast hosting platform like Spotify for Podcasters (formerly Anchor). They'll generate the RSS feed for you automatically, host your audio files, and help you distribute to major podcast directories - all for free. You can always migrate to a paid service later if you need more features.
Would you like help understanding how to set up a podcast RSS feed or recommendations for specific free platforms?Can you generate the rss feed code for me?Jan 19Absolutely! I can generate RSS feed code for your podcast. To create a proper RSS feed, I'll need some information from you:
Required information:

Podcast title
Podcast description
Author/host name
Podcast category (e.g., Technology, Comedy, Education, etc.)
Language (e.g., en-us for English)
Your email address (for the feed)
Podcast artwork URL (square image, at least 1400x1400px recommended)

For each episode, I'll need:

Episode title
Episode description
Audio file URL (where your MP3 is hosted)
Publication date
Episode duration
File size (in bytes)

Once you provide this information, I'll create a complete, valid podcast RSS feed in XML format that you can use. You can then:

Upload it to your web server
Submit the feed URL to podcast directories like Apple Podcasts, Spotify, etc.

Go ahead and share whatever details you have, and I'll generate the RSS feed code for you!cover image is here. https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119/WS.jpgJan 19Great! I can see you have your cover image hosted. Now I just need the other details to generate your RSS feed:
Podcast Information:

Podcast title: ?
Podcast description: ?
Author/host name: ?
Podcast category: ? (e.g., Technology, Comedy, Education, True Crime, Business, etc.)
Language: ? (I'll assume en-us unless you specify otherwise)
Contact email: ?

Episode Information:
For each episode you want to include:

Episode title: ?
Episode description: ?
Audio file URL: ? (where is your MP3 file hosted?)
Publication date: ?
Duration: ? (format: HH:MM:SS)
File size: ? (in bytes - if you don't know this, I can help you figure it out)

Once you provide these details, I'll create the complete RSS feed code for you in an artifact that you can copy and use right away!the first episode is here https://dn710300.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-1-c-where-the-c-goes/E1-C%20Where%20the%20C%20Goes.mp3Jan 19Fetched: https://dn710300.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-1-c-where-the-c-goes/E1-C%20Where%20the%20C%20Goes.mp3https://dn710300.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-1-c-where-the-c-goes/E1-C%20Where%20the%20C%20Goes.mp3dn710300.ca.archive.orgDonePerfect! I can see the audio file is accessible. Based on the filename, it looks like your first episode is titled "E1-C Where the C Goes" (or similar).
I still need a few more details to create a complete RSS feed:
Podcast Information:

Podcast title: ?
Podcast description: ? (A brief description of what your podcast is about)
Author/host name: ?
Podcast category: ? (What type of podcast is this?)
Contact email: ?
Language: en-us? (or another language code)

Episode 1 Details:

Episode title: "C Where the C Goes" or something else?
Episode description: ? (What is this episode about?)
Publication date: ? (e.g., January 15, 2026)
Duration: ? (How long is the episode? HH:MM:SS format)

If you want, you can just give me the basics and I'll create a template RSS feed that you can customize later. Or provide as much detail as you have and I'll make it more complete!second episode is here https://ia800402.us.archive.org/19/items/wordle-spoiler-e-2-how-do-you-spell-relief/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e2%20-%20How%20Do%20You%20Spell%20Relief%3F.mp3Jan 19Great! I can see you have two episodes:

"C Where the C Goes"
"How Do You Spell Relief?"

It looks like this might be a podcast about words, spelling, or language (possibly related to Wordle?).
I can create a basic RSS feed template for you now with the information I have, and you can fill in the remaining details. However, it would be really helpful to know at minimum:
Just the essentials:

Podcast title: ? (e.g., "Wordle Spoiler" or whatever you want to call it)
Your name/host name: ?
A brief description: ? (One sentence about what the podcast covers)
Your email: ? (This is required for podcast directories)

Episode details I can guess but would like to confirm:

Episode 1: "C Where the C Goes"
Episode 2: "How Do You Spell Relief?"
Are these the correct titles?
Do you know the duration of each episode?
Publication dates?

If you want, I can create a template right now with placeholder information that you can customize, or you can give me these few details and I'll make it complete and ready to use. What would you prefer?Podcast title is: Wordle Spoiler and it is about spelling, language, and games!Jan 19Excellent! I'm getting a clearer picture. A few more quick details and I can generate your RSS feed:
Still need:

Your name/host name: ? (How should you be credited as the host/author?)
Your email: ? (Required for podcast directories - can be any email you want to use)
Podcast description: Would something like this work? "A podcast about spelling, language, and games including Wordle and word puzzles" (or you can provide your own)

Episode details:

Episode 1 title: "C Where the C Goes" - correct?
Episode 2 title: "How Do You Spell Relief?" - correct?
Publication dates: When did you (or will you) publish each episode?
Episode durations: Do you know how long each episode is? (If not, I can leave this as a placeholder)
Episode descriptions: Brief description of what each episode covers? (Optional but recommended)

Once I have at least your name and email, I can generate the RSS feed for you! The more details you provide, the more complete it will be.The hosts and creators for all the shows and content is Abby Manock and Casey OpstadJan 19Perfect! Just need one more essential detail:
Contact email: ? (This is required for podcast RSS feeds - it can be a general contact email for the podcast)
And optional but helpful:

Publication dates for episodes 1 & 2: ? (e.g., "January 10, 2026" and "January 17, 2026" or whatever dates)
Episode durations: ? (If you don't know, I can put placeholders)
Brief episode descriptions: ? (Optional - what each episode is about)

Once you give me an email address, I can generate the RSS feed! I'll use what we have:

Title: Wordle Spoiler
Hosts/Creators: Abby Manock and Casey Opstad
Description: A podcast about spelling, language, and games
Cover art: https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119/WS.jpg
Episode 1: "C Where the C Goes"
Episode 2: "How Do You Spell Relief?"

What email should I use for the feed?contact email is wordlespoilerpodcast@gmail.comJan 19Perfect! I have everything I need to create your RSS feed. Let me generate it for you now:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://aPerfect! I've created your RSS feed for the Wordle Spoiler podcast. Here's what you need to know:
What I included:
✅ Podcast title: "Wordle Spoiler"
✅ Hosts: Abby Manock and Casey Opstad
✅ Contact email: wordlespoilerpodcast@gmail.com
✅ Cover image from Archive.org
✅ Both episodes with their audio file URLs
✅ Proper iTunes/Apple Podcasts tags
What you should update:

Episode durations: I put placeholder times of 15 minutes. Update the <itunes:duration> tags with actual lengths (format: HH:MM:SS)
File sizes: I put placeholder values of 10000000 bytes. Update the length attribute in the <enclosure> tags with actual file sizes
Publication dates: I used January 12 and 19, 2026. Update <pubDate> if different
Episode descriptions: Add more detailed descriptions of what each episode covers

Next steps:

Save this as a .xml file (e.g., wordle-spoiler.xml)
Upload it to a web server where it's publicly accessible
Submit the RSS feed URL to podcast directories (Apple Podcasts, Spotify, etc.)

Need help with any of these steps or want me to update any of the placeholder information?publication date for episode one is Sunday January 18th, 2026Jan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 2       <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>Updated! Episode 1 now shows Sunday, January 18th, 2026 as the publication date.
What about Episode 2 - when was/will that be published? And do you happen to know the actual durations of your episodes? If you have the MP3 files on your computer, you can check the file properties to get the exact duration and file size.publication date for episode two is Monday January 19th, 2026Jan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 3       <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>Perfect! Episode 2 is already set to Monday, January 19th, 2026 (today), so that's all set.
Now you just need to update:

Episode durations - the actual length of each episode (currently showing placeholder 00:15:00)
File sizes - the actual size in bytes for each MP3 file (currently showing placeholder 10000000)

Do you know the actual duration and file size for each episode? If you have the files on your computer, you can:

Duration: Right-click the MP3 → Properties → Details tab (Windows) or Get Info (Mac)
File size: Shows in the same place, usually in bytes

Once you have those, I can update the RSS feed to be completely accurate!episode one is 9 mintues and 17 seconds longJan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 4       <itunes:duration>00:09:17</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

  </channel>Updated! Episode 1 now shows the correct duration of 9 minutes and 17 seconds.
What about Episode 2 - how long is that one?episode two is 6 minutes and 56 secondsJan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 5       <itunes:duration>00:06:56</itunes:duration>Perfect! Episode 2 is now updated to 6 minutes and 56 seconds.
The RSS feed is looking great! The only remaining placeholders are the file sizes (currently showing 10000000 bytes for both episodes). If you know the actual file sizes in bytes, I can update those too. Otherwise, the RSS feed should work fine as-is - most podcast directories will auto-detect the file size when they fetch the audio files.
Your RSS feed is ready to use! You can:

Save it as an .xml file
Upload it to a publicly accessible web location
Submit the feed URL to Apple Podcasts, Spotify, and other directories

Need help with anything else for your podcast?episode one is 17.8 mbJan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 6       <enclosure url="https://dn710300.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-1-c-where-the-c-goes/E1-C%20Where%20the%20C%20Goes.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="18664652"/>Great! I've updated Episode 1's file size to 18,664,652 bytes (17.8 MB).
What's the file size for Episode 2?episode 2 is 13.3mbJan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 7       <enclosure url="https://ia800402.us.archive.org/19/items/wordle-spoiler-e-2-how-do-you-spell-relief/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e2%20-%20How%20Do%20You%20Spell%20Relief%3F.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13945241"/>Perfect! Your RSS feed is now complete with all the accurate information:
✅ Podcast title and description
✅ Hosts: Abby Manock and Casey Opstad
✅ Contact email
✅ Cover image
✅ Episode 1: "C Where the C Goes" - 9:17, 17.8 MB, published Jan 18, 2026
✅ Episode 2: "How Do You Spell Relief?" - 6:56, 13.3 MB, published Jan 19, 2026
Your RSS feed is ready to go!
Next steps:

Copy the XML code from the artifact
Save it as a file (e.g., wordle-spoiler.xml or feed.xml)
Upload it to a web server where it's publicly accessible (you could use Archive.org, GitHub Pages, your own website, etc.)
Once it's uploaded, submit the feed URL to:

Apple Podcasts (via Podcasts Connect)
Spotify for Podcasters
Google Podcasts
And other podcast directories



Would you like help with any of these next steps?yesJan 19Great! Let me walk you through the next steps:
Step 1: Save the RSS Feed File

Copy all the XML code from the artifact above
Open a text editor (Notepad on Windows, TextEdit on Mac, or any code editor)
Paste the code
Save it as feed.xml or wordle-spoiler.xml (make sure it has the .xml extension)

Step 2: Upload to a Public Location
Since your episodes are already on Archive.org, that's a great place to host your RSS feed too! Here are your options:
Option A: Archive.org (Recommended since you're already using it)

Go to https://archive.org
Sign in or create an account
Click "Upload"
Upload your feed.xml file to the same collection as your episodes
Once uploaded, you'll get a public URL like: https://archive.org/download/your-collection-name/feed.xml

Option B: GitHub Pages (Free and reliable)

Create a free GitHub account
Create a new repository
Upload your feed.xml file
Enable GitHub Pages in settings
Your feed will be at: https://yourusername.github.io/repository-name/feed.xml

Option C: Your own website
If you have a website, just upload the XML file to your web server.
Which option sounds best for you?I just sign into Github, so let's use thatJan 19Perfect! Let's set up your RSS feed on GitHub. Here's what to do:
Step 1: Create a New Repository

Go to https://github.com and make sure you're signed in
Click the "+" icon in the top right corner
Select "New repository"
Name it something like wordle-spoiler-podcast or podcast-feed
Make sure it's set to Public (required for RSS feeds)
Check the box "Add a README file" (this makes the next steps easier)
Click "Create repository"

Step 2: Upload Your RSS Feed

In your new repository, click "Add file" → "Create new file"
Name the file feed.xml
Copy the XML code from the artifact above and paste it into the file
Scroll down and click "Commit new file"

Step 3: Enable GitHub Pages

In your repository, click "Settings" (top menu)
Scroll down the left sidebar and click "Pages"
Under "Source", select "Deploy from a branch"
Under "Branch", select "main" and "/ (root)"
Click "Save"
Wait a minute or two, then refresh the page - you'll see a URL like: https://yourusername.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/

Your RSS feed URL will be: https://yourusername.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Let me know when you've got the repository created and I'll help with the next steps!commit to changes or commit to new fileJan 19Click "Commit new file" since you're creating a new file (the feed.xml).
"Commit changes" would only show up if you were editing an existing file.
Once you click "Commit new file", your feed.xml will be saved to your repository!I don't see commit new file in GithubJan 19No worries! GitHub's interface has changed. You should see a green button that says either:

"Commit changes..." or
"Commit new file"

It's usually at the bottom of the page after you've pasted your XML code into the file editor.
Can you tell me what you see at the bottom of the page? There should be a green button - what does it say?
Alternatively, are you using the web interface or GitHub Desktop? If you're on the web, make sure you:

Named the file feed.xml at the top
Pasted the XML code into the text box
Scrolled all the way to the bottom

What do you see?I committed to changes and it workedJan 19Excellent! Your feed.xml file is now in your repository.
Next Step: Enable GitHub Pages
Now we need to make it publicly accessible:

Click on "Settings" at the top of your repository page (it's in the top menu bar)
In the left sidebar, scroll down and click "Pages" (under the "Code and automation" section)
Under "Source", select "Deploy from a branch"
Under "Branch", change the dropdown from "None" to "main" (or "master")
Make sure the folder is set to "/ (root)"
Click "Save"

After a minute or two, refresh the Settings → Pages page and you should see a message like: "Your site is live at https://yourusername.github.io/repository-name/"
Your RSS feed URL will be: https://yourusername.github.io/repository-name/feed.xml
Let me know once you've enabled Pages and I'll help you submit it to podcast directories!it says it's live at https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/Jan 19Perfect! Your RSS feed is now live at:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
You can test it by visiting that URL in your browser - you should see your XML code.
Step 4: Submit to Podcast Directories
Now let's get your podcast on the major platforms:
Apple Podcasts (Most important - other platforms pull from here)

Go to https://podcastsconnect.apple.com
Sign in with your Apple ID (or create one)
Click the "+" button to add a podcast
Enter your RSS feed URL: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Apple will validate it and add your podcast (usually takes 24-48 hours)

Spotify for Podcasters

Go to https://podcasters.spotify.com
Sign in or create an account
Click "Get Started"
Select "Import your podcast"
Enter your RSS feed URL
Follow the verification steps

Other Platforms (Optional but recommended)

Google Podcasts: Submit via https://podcastsmanager.google.com
Amazon Music/Audible: https://podcasters.amazon.com
iHeartRadio: https://www.iheart.com/podcast-partners/
Pocket Casts, Overcast, and many others automatically pull from Apple Podcasts

Would you like help with submitting to any of these platforms?I don't see where I'm suppose to import my podcast in SpoitfyJan 19Let me help you navigate Spotify for Podcasters. The interface can be a bit tricky. Here's what to look for:
If you're on the main page:

Look for a button that says "Get started" or "Add your podcast"
You might see options like "Create a podcast" or "Import a podcast" - click "Import a podcast" or "I already have a podcast"

If you don't see those options:

Try going directly to: https://podcasters.spotify.com/pod/dashboard
Or look for "+ Add a show" or similar button

What do you currently see on your screen? Are you on:

The welcome/landing page?
A dashboard?
Something else?

Sometimes Spotify's interface changes, so if you can describe what you're seeing, I can guide you more specifically. Alternatively, you could tell me what buttons or options are visible on your current page.trying to add an episode in spoifty after I started using this rss feed https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml but I can'tJan 19Ah, I see the issue! When you import an RSS feed into Spotify, you don't manually add episodes through Spotify's interface. The episodes come automatically from your RSS feed.
Here's how it works:
Your RSS feed is the source of truth - Spotify (and all other podcast platforms) automatically pull episodes from your RSS feed. You don't add episodes through Spotify's dashboard.
To add new episodes in the future:

Upload the new episode audio file to Archive.org (or wherever you host it)
Edit your feed.xml file on GitHub
Add a new <item> section for the new episode (copying the format of episodes 1 and 2)
Commit the changes to GitHub
Within a few hours, Spotify (and other platforms) will automatically detect the new episode and add it

Right now, your feed already has 2 episodes, so Spotify should show both "C Where the C Goes" and "How Do You Spell Relief?" automatically.
Questions:

Can you see your 2 existing episodes in Spotify's dashboard?
Are you trying to add a third episode, or are the first two not showing up?

Let me know what you're seeing and I can help troubleshoot!Apple podcast is having issues with my image for the podcastJan 19Apple Podcasts has strict requirements for podcast artwork. Let me check your image and see what might be the issue.Failed to fetch: https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119/WS.jpgFailed to fetch https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119/WS.jpgDoneLet me search for Apple Podcasts' image requirements to help you troubleshoot:Searched the webApple Podcasts artwork image requirements specifications10 resultsPodcast Artwork Requirements - Apple Communitydiscussions.apple.comArtwork guide - Apple Podcasts for Creatorspodcasters.apple.comEnsuring Podcast Artwork Meets Apple Podcasts Requirements – SoundCloud Help Centerhelp.soundcloud.comSpecs for podcast cover art on Apple Podcasts, Spotify etc | Transistor Helpsupport.transistor.fmPodcast Artwork Specifications | Captivate Help and Supporthelp.captivate.fmPodcast Cover Art Size Preview - Check Cover Art on Podcast Apps | OnlyPodonlypod.comPodcast Artwork Size to be Featured - Apple Communitydiscussions.apple.comHow to Create Podcast Artwork: A Complete Guide - Spreaker Blogblog.spreaker.comApple (Previously iTunes) Podcasts Submission Requirements | Blubrryblubrry.comPodcast Artwork: Logo + Cover Art (with Apple Artwork Guidelines) – 48hourslogo Blogwww.48hourslogo.comDoneBased on Apple Podcasts' requirements, here are the most common issues with podcast artwork:
Apple Podcasts Image Requirements:

Must be at least 1400x1400 pixels and no larger than 3000x3000 pixels SoundCloud
Must be square (same width and height)
File size must be below 500KB Apple Community
Format: JPG or PNG
PNG images must be saved in RGB color space, not CMYK Blubrry
Must be hosted on a server that supports HTTP head requests

What's likely wrong with your image:
The most common issues are:

File size too large - The image file might be over 500KB
Wrong dimensions - Not square or outside the 1400-3000 pixel range
Wrong color space - If it's a PNG, it might be in CMYK instead of RGB

How to fix it:

Download your image from Archive.org
Check its properties:

Is it square?
What are the pixel dimensions?
What's the file size?


Use a free tool like:

TinyPNG (https://tinypng.com) to reduce file size
Canva or Photoshop to resize to 1400x1400 or 3000x3000 pixels
Make sure it's saved as RGB (not CMYK) if using PNG



What specific error message is Apple Podcasts showing you? That will help me pinpoint the exact issue!Art - Artwork must be 3000 x 3000 pixels, JPG or PNG, in RGB color space, and hosted on a server that allows HTTP head requestJan 19Apple is requiring your artwork to be exactly 3000 x 3000 pixels. Your current image is likely smaller than that.
Here's how to fix it:
Option 1: Resize Your Current Image

Download your image from https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119/WS.jpg
Use a free tool to resize it to 3000x3000 pixels:

Canva (https://canva.com) - free, easy to use
Photoshop or GIMP if you have them
Online resizer like https://www.simpleimageresizer.com


Make sure it's:

Exactly 3000 x 3000 pixels
JPG or PNG format
RGB color space (not CMYK)
Under 500KB file size


Re-upload the new 3000x3000 image to Archive.org
Update the image URL in your RSS feed if needed

Option 2: I Can Help You Update the Feed
Once you have a new 3000x3000 image:

Upload it to Archive.org (or GitHub with your RSS feed)
Get the new URL
Tell me the new URL and I'll update your RSS feed with it

Quick question: Do you have image editing software, or would you like me to recommend the easiest free tool to resize your image?here is the new logo image for the podcast https://archive.org/details/ws_20260119_20260119Jan 19Fetched: WS : Free Download, Borrow, and Streaming : Internet ArchiveWS : Free Download, Borrow, and Streaming : Internet Archivearchive.orgDonePerfect! I can see your new image. The direct URL to the image file is:
https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119_20260119/WS.jpg
Let me update your RSS feed with this new image URL:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS FeedCode ∙ Version 8     <itunes:image href="https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119_20260119/WS.jpg"/>Great! I've updated your RSS feed with the new image URL. Now you need to:
Update the feed.xml file on GitHub

Go to your GitHub repository: https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on the feed.xml file
Click the pencil icon (Edit) in the top right
Delete all the old content and copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Paste the new content
Scroll down and click "Commit changes"

Once you commit the changes, GitHub Pages will automatically update your feed (might take a minute or two).
Then try submitting to Apple Podcasts again with the same URL: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
The new image should meet Apple's requirements. Let me know if you still get an error!Apple is not letting me update to this linkhttps://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xmlJan 19Apple Podcasts can be tricky about updating RSS feeds once you've already submitted one. Here are a few things to try:
Option 1: Wait and Try Again
Sometimes Apple's validation is cached. Wait 10-15 minutes after updating your GitHub feed, then try submitting again.
Option 2: Clear the Validation

In Apple Podcasts Connect, try to remove or delete the podcast submission (if it's still pending)
Wait a few minutes
Submit the feed URL again fresh

Option 3: Force GitHub to Update
Sometimes GitHub Pages takes a bit to update. To force it:

Go to your repository on GitHub
Make a tiny edit to feed.xml (like add a space somewhere, then remove it)
Commit the change
Wait 2-3 minutes for GitHub Pages to rebuild

Option 4: Verify the Feed is Updated
Let's make sure the feed actually updated on GitHub:

Visit https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml in your browser
Search the page (Ctrl+F or Cmd+F) for the new image URL: ws_20260119_20260119
Do you see it in the feed?

What specific error message is Apple showing you now? That will help me figure out what's still wrong. Is it:

Still the image error?
A different error?
Just not accepting the URL at all?
Art - Artwork must be 3000 x 3000 pixels, JPG or PNG, in RGB color space, and hosted on a server that allows HTTP head requestsJan 19The error is still about the artwork, which means either:

The new image still isn't 3000x3000 pixels, OR
GitHub Pages hasn't updated yet with your new feed, OR
The image file itself isn't the right size

Let me help you check. Can you tell me:
Did you resize the image to exactly 3000x3000 pixels before uploading it to Archive.org?
If not, that's the issue - you need to:

Download the image
Resize it to exactly 3000 x 3000 pixels using:

Canva (free, easiest): https://www.canva.com/create/album-covers/
Or Photoshop/GIMP
Or an online tool like https://www.birme.net (bulk image resizer)


Make sure it's saved as JPG or PNG in RGB color mode
Keep file size under 500KB
Re-upload to Archive.org

OR - let me verify your GitHub feed actually updated:
Go to https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml in your browser right now.
Look at the <itunes:image href="..."/> line. Does it say:

ws_20260119_20260119/WS.jpg (NEW - correct)
OR ws_20260119/WS.jpg (OLD - wrong)

Which one do you see?Do you think it's the Head requests?Jan 19Good question! It's possible, but Archive.org usually supports HTTP HEAD requests just fine since it's designed for public file hosting.
However, let me help you test this. The easiest way to rule things out is:
Quick Test: Host the Image on GitHub Instead
Since your RSS feed is already on GitHub Pages (which definitely supports HEAD requests), let's put your image there too:

Go to your GitHub repository: https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click "Add file" → "Upload files"
Upload your podcast artwork image (make sure it's 3000x3000 pixels first!)
Name it something simple like artwork.jpg or cover.jpg
Commit the file

Then your image URL would be:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/artwork.jpg
I can then update your RSS feed to use this URL instead.
But first - the most likely issue is still the image dimensions.
Can you check: What are the actual pixel dimensions of your current image?

Right-click the image file on your computer
Look at Properties/Get Info
What does it say for dimensions?

If it's not exactly 3000x3000, that's definitely the problem, not the HEAD requests.image is here WS.jpgJan 19I can't see the file from here since you're showing it on your local computer. But I can help you check if it's the right size and fix it if needed!
To check the image size:

Right-click on WS.jpg on your computer
Select "Properties" (Windows) or "Get Info" (Mac)
Look for "Dimensions" or "Image Size"
What does it say? (e.g., "3000 x 3000" or something else?)

If it's NOT 3000 x 3000:
The easiest way to resize it is:
Option 1: Use Canva (Free, No Download)

Go to https://www.canva.com
Sign up/log in (free)
Create a Custom Size design: 3000 x 3000 pixels
Upload your WS.jpg image
Drag it to fill the entire 3000x3000 canvas
Download as JPG
Upload the new file to Archive.org or GitHub

Option 2: Use an Online Resizer

Go to https://www.birme.net
Upload your WS.jpg
Set width and height to 3000
Download the resized image

Once you have a proper 3000x3000 pixel image, upload it and give me the new URL - I'll update your RSS feed!
What dimensions does your current image show?Jan 19Perfect! I can see your podcast artwork - it looks great! The Wordle-style grid with "WORDLE SPOILER" is very fitting for your podcast theme.
Now I need to know: What are the pixel dimensions of this image?
To find out:

Right-click the image file
Select "Properties" (Windows) or "Get Info" (Mac)
Look for dimensions - it should say something like "1500 x 1500" or "3000 x 3000"

If it's anything other than 3000 x 3000 pixels, that's why Apple is rejecting it.
Once you tell me the current size, I can guide you through resizing it to exactly 3000x3000 pixels, which is what Apple requires.
What size does it show?3000 x 3000 pixelsJan 19Great! So the image IS 3000x3000 pixels. That means the issue is likely one of these:

Your RSS feed on GitHub hasn't updated yet with the new image URL
Apple's cache hasn't refreshed
The HTTP HEAD request issue (less likely but possible)

Let's troubleshoot:
Step 1: Verify Your Feed Updated on GitHub
Go to this URL in your browser: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Press Ctrl+F (or Cmd+F) and search for "itunes:image"
Does it show:

https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119_20260119/WS.jpg ✓ (correct - new)
OR https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119/WS.jpg ✗ (wrong - old)

What do you see?
Step 2: If It's Still the Old URL
You need to update your feed.xml file on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click feed.xml
Click the pencil icon to edit
Copy the ENTIRE updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything in the file
Commit changes

Let me know what you see when you check the feed URL!It worked now in Apple POdcastsJan 19Excellent! 🎉 Your podcast is now submitted to Apple Podcasts!
It typically takes 24-48 hours for Apple to review and approve your podcast. Once approved, it'll be available on Apple Podcasts, and you'll get a notification.
What's Next?
1. Submit to Spotify (if you haven't finished that yet)

Go to https://podcasters.spotify.com
Import your RSS feed: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml

2. Other Platforms to Consider:

Google Podcasts: https://podcastsmanager.google.com
Amazon Music/Audible: https://podcasters.amazon.com
Stitcher: Usually pulls from Apple automatically
iHeartRadio: https://www.iheart.com/podcast-partners/

3. Adding Future Episodes:
When you're ready to add Episode 3 (or more):

Upload the audio file to Archive.org
Edit your feed.xml on GitHub
Copy one of the existing <item> sections
Update it with the new episode info (title, URL, date, duration, file size)
Add it at the TOP (newest episodes go first)
Commit the changes
Platforms will automatically detect the new episode within a few hours

Congratulations on launching "Wordle Spoiler"! Good luck with the podcast, Abby and Casey! 🎙️can you show me your most recent rss feed code?Jan 19Absolutely! Here's the complete, up-to-date RSS feed code with all the corrections we made:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://aThere you go! This is the complete, current RSS feed with all the updates:
✅ Updated artwork URL: https://archive.org/download/ws_20260119_20260119/WS.jpg
✅ Episode 1: "C Where the C Goes" - 9:17, 17.8 MB, Jan 18, 2026
✅ Episode 2: "How Do You Spell Relief?" - 6:56, 13.3 MB, Jan 19, 2026
✅ Correct file sizes in bytes
✅ All podcast information
This is what should be in your feed.xml file on GitHub. If you need to make sure it's up to date, you can copy this entire code and replace what's in your GitHub file!what's the latest link to my rss feedJan 19Your RSS feed is live at:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
This is the URL you'll use to submit your podcast to all the different platforms (Apple Podcasts, Spotify, Google Podcasts, etc.).If I change the main desciption of the show in my RSS feed file will it update at all the podcast platforms?Jan 19Yes, it will update on most podcast platforms, but with some important caveats:
How It Works:
Yes, it will update on:

Spotify
Google Podcasts
Most smaller platforms
RSS readers

These platforms regularly check your RSS feed (usually every few hours to once a day) and will pick up the new description automatically.
Apple Podcasts is tricky:

Apple caches podcast information heavily
Some fields (like the main description) may take days or even weeks to update
Apple prioritizes what you enter in their Podcasts Connect dashboard over what's in the RSS feed for certain fields
For faster updates to Apple Podcasts, you can manually edit the description in Podcasts Connect (https://podcastsconnect.apple.com)

Best Practice:

Update your RSS feed - This ensures all platforms eventually get the new description
Also update Apple Podcasts Connect manually - Log in and edit the description there for faster Apple updates
Wait 24-48 hours - Most platforms will pick up the changes

To Update Your RSS Feed:

Edit the <description> and <itunes:summary> tags in your feed.xml on GitHub
Commit the changes
Platforms will automatically detect it on their next check

So yes, update your RSS feed and it will propagate, but Apple may be slow. Want help updating the description?WORDLE SPOILER is a recap, review and in depth analysis of the daily Wordle experience. WARNING: Do not listen to this podcast if you haven’t done your Wordle yet today! WE WILL SPOIL IT! can you make this the main description?Jan 19Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 2     <itunes:summary>WORDLE SPOILER is a recap, review and in depth analysis of the daily Wordle experience. WARNING: Do not listen to this podcast if you haven't done your Wordle yet today! WE WILL SPOIL IT!</itunes:summary>
    <description>WORDLE SPerfect! I've updated the main description to your new text with the spoiler warning.
Now you need to update your feed.xml file on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything in the file with the new code
Scroll down and click "Commit changes"

Once you commit, the platforms will pick up the new description on their next refresh (usually within 24 hours). For Apple Podcasts, you may also want to update it manually in Podcasts Connect for a faster update there.
The new description is much better - it clearly explains what the podcast is about AND warns people about spoilers! 👍doneJan 19Excellent! Your RSS feed is now updated with the new description.
What Happens Next:

Spotify, Google, and other platforms: Will automatically pick up the new description within 24 hours
Apple Podcasts: May take longer (up to a week), or you can manually update it in Podcasts Connect for faster results

Your podcast is all set! 🎉
Quick Recap of What You Have:
✅ RSS Feed: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
✅ 2 episodes published
✅ 3000x3000 artwork
✅ New spoiler warning description
✅ Submitted to Apple Podcasts (pending approval)
For future episodes, just remember to:

Upload audio to Archive.org
Edit feed.xml on GitHub
Add a new <item> section at the top with the episode details
Commit the changes

Is there anything else you need help with for your podcast?Abby is changing the description more, so....just a secondJan 19No problem! Take your time. Just let me know what the new description should be and I'll update it for you. 👍she just added in-depth the hypenJan 19Got it! So "in-depth" instead of "in depth". Let me update that:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 3     <itunes:summary>WORDLE SPOILER is a recap, review and in-depth analysis of the daily Wordle experience. WARNING: Do not listen to this podcast if you haven't done your Wordle yet today! WE WILL SPOIL IT!</itunes:summary>
    <description>WORDLE SDone! "in-depth" now has the hyphen. Just copy the updated code from the artifact and update your GitHub feed.xml file when you're ready!doneJan 19Perfect! Your RSS feed is updated with "in-depth" (hyphenated).
Let me know if Abby has any other changes, or if you need help with anything else for the podcast! 👍what are main podcast platformsJan 19Here are the main podcast platforms you should submit to:
Essential Platforms (Must-Have):

Apple Podcasts - The biggest, most important platform. Other platforms often pull data from here.
Spotify - Second largest, rapidly growing
YouTube Music/YouTube Podcasts - Growing quickly, especially for video podcasts

Important Secondary Platforms:

Amazon Music/Audible - Large audience, owned by Amazon
Google Podcasts - Being merged into YouTube Music but still active
iHeartRadio - Major radio company with podcast platform
Stitcher - Popular with podcast listeners
TuneIn - Good for radio/podcast discovery

Other Popular Platforms:

Pocket Casts - Popular podcast app (usually auto-pulls from Apple)
Overcast - Popular iOS app (auto-pulls from Apple)
Castbox - Growing international platform
Podcast Addict - Popular Android app
Player FM - Good reach
Podchaser - Podcast discovery platform

Good News:
Many of these (like Pocket Casts, Overcast, Castro, etc.) automatically pull podcasts that are in Apple Podcasts, so once you're approved by Apple, you'll appear in many places automatically.
Priority order for submission:

Apple Podcasts ✅ (you've done this!)
Spotify (in progress?)
YouTube Music
Amazon Music
iHeartRadio

Want help submitting to any of these?can you help me do a google podcast?Jan 19Actually, there's an important update about Google Podcasts:
Google Podcasts is being shut down! Google migrated everything to YouTube Music in 2024, and Google Podcasts no longer exists as a standalone platform.
Instead, submit to YouTube Music/YouTube Podcasts:
Here's how:

Go to YouTube Studio at https://studio.youtube.com
Sign in with your Google account
In the left sidebar, look for "Podcasts" (or it might be under "Content")
Click "Get Started" or "Add Podcast"
Enter your RSS feed URL: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Follow the prompts to verify and set up your podcast

Benefits of YouTube Music:

Reaches both YouTube Music listeners AND shows up in YouTube search
You can optionally add video later if you want
Integrated with the massive YouTube audience
Completely free

YouTube Music is actually a much better platform to be on now than Google Podcasts ever was, since it has way more users!
Want to try submitting to YouTube Music, or would you like help with a different platform like Amazon Music or iHeartRadio?new image for the podcastJan 19Great! What's the URL for the new image?
And just to confirm - is it:

3000 x 3000 pixels?
JPG or PNG format?
Uploaded to Archive.org or somewhere else?

Give me the link and I'll update your RSS feed!Jan 19I love the hand-drawn artwork! It's got a great personal, artistic touch with the Wordle grid and the green/yellow color scheme. Very charming!
However, I need you to:

Upload this image to Archive.org (or GitHub) so it has a public URL
Make sure it's 3000 x 3000 pixels before uploading (Apple Podcasts requirement)
Save it as JPG or PNG

To upload to Archive.org:

Go to https://archive.org
Sign in
Click "Upload"
Upload your image file
Once uploaded, get the direct link to the image (it'll be something like https://archive.org/download/your-collection/filename.jpg)

To resize to 3000x3000:

Use Canva, Photoshop, or an online tool like https://www.birme.net
Make sure it's exactly 3000 x 3000 pixels

Once you have the URL, send it to me and I'll update your RSS feed!3000 x 3000 JPGJan 19Perfect! Now you just need to upload it to Archive.org (or GitHub) and give me the public URL.
To upload to Archive.org:

Go to https://archive.org and sign in
Click "Upload"
Upload your 3000x3000 JPG file
Once it's uploaded, you'll get a URL like: https://archive.org/download/collection-name/filename.jpg
Copy that URL and send it to me

OR upload to GitHub (if that's easier):

Go to your repository: https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click "Add file" → "Upload files"
Upload the image (name it something like artwork.jpg)
Commit the file
The URL will be: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/artwork.jpg

Once you have the URL, send it to me and I'll update your RSS feed right away!https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpgJan 19Perfect! Let me update your RSS feed with the new artwork URL:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 4     <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg"/>Done! I've updated your RSS feed with the new hand-drawn artwork. Now you need to update your feed.xml file on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Once you commit, the new artwork will appear on all podcast platforms within 24 hours. The hand-drawn style looks great - really gives your podcast a unique, personal feel! 🎨doneJan 19Awesome! Your RSS feed now has the new hand-drawn artwork. 🎨
The platforms will pick up the new image within 24 hours. For Apple Podcasts, it might take a bit longer, but it will update.
Your podcast is looking great! Is there anything else you need help with?I need to change the episode artwork to the same image as the main imageJan 19Got it! I'll update both episodes to use the same artwork as the main podcast image.Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 5     <!-- Episode 2 -->
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Spell Relief?</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 2 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 2: HoPerfect! I've added the <itunes:image> tag to both episodes so they'll use the same hand-drawn artwork as the main podcast image.
Now update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Once you commit, both episodes will display with the new artwork! 🎨got it. thanksJan 19You're welcome! Your podcast is all set up now. Good luck with "Wordle Spoiler" - I hope it does great! 🎙️
Feel free to come back if you need help adding new episodes or making any other changes. Happy podcasting, Abby and Casey! 👍wheres the spoitfy link to podcastersJan 19Here's the Spotify for Podcasters link:
https://podcasters.spotify.com
Once you're there:

Sign in or create an account
Look for "Get started" or "Add your podcast"
Select "I already have a podcast" or "Import a podcast"
Enter your RSS feed URL: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Follow the verification steps

Let me know if you run into any issues!does the shared link to the podcast have a separate image? can you make sure all images across the podcast rss is only the main image?Jan 19Good question! Let me check the RSS feed. The "shared link" image you're seeing might be coming from a different tag in the RSS feed.
Looking at the current feed, I see we have:

Main podcast image: ✅ <itunes:image>
Episode images: ✅ <itunes:image> for each episode

All of these are set to the same image: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg
However, there might be one more place we need to add the image - the channel-level <image> tag (different from <itunes:image>). Some platforms use this for sharing. Let me add it:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 6     <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://archive.org/details/ws_20260119</link>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright 2026 Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.ioPerfect! I've added the standard RSS <image> tag to ensure all platforms use the same artwork for sharing and display.
Now your RSS feed has the same image in all possible places:

✅ Main podcast <itunes:image>
✅ Main podcast <image> (for RSS readers and sharing)
✅ Episode 1 <itunes:image>
✅ Episode 2 <itunes:image>

Update your feed.xml on GitHub with the code from the artifact above, and you should be all set! Every image reference will be the hand-drawn artwork.looks like it workedJan 19Awesome! 🎉 Glad it's all working now. Your podcast should have consistent artwork everywhere - on all platforms, in shares, and for each episode.
Anything else you need help with?I've done apple, spotify, amazon music, and youtube music. Are there anymore platforms you'd recommend?Jan 19Great job! You've already covered the biggest platforms. Here are a few more worth considering:
Highly Recommended:

iHeartRadio - https://www.iheart.com/podcast-partners/

Major platform with huge reach, especially in the US
Easy submission process


Podcast Index - https://podcastindex.org

Open podcast directory that feeds into many apps
Supports the independent podcast ecosystem



Good to Have:

Podchaser - https://www.podchaser.com/creators

Good for podcast discovery and reviews
Helps with discoverability


TuneIn - https://tunein.com/podcasters/

Popular for radio and podcast streaming
Good international reach


Deezer - https://podcasters.deezer.com

Popular in Europe and internationally
Growing podcast platform



The Good News:
Many smaller platforms (Pocket Casts, Overcast, Castro, Castbox, Player FM, etc.) automatically pull from Apple Podcasts, so you're already on those without doing anything extra!
My recommendation: Add iHeartRadio for sure. The others are optional but can help with discovery.
You've already done the heavy lifting with the big four! Want help submitting to iHeartRadio?https://www.iheart.com/podcast-partners/ this doesn't workJan 19You're right - that link doesn't seem to be working. iHeartRadio has changed how they handle podcast submissions.
Here's the current way to submit to iHeartRadio:
iHeartRadio now uses a different submission process:
Try this link instead: https://www.iheartpodcastnetwork.com/
Or you can try contacting them directly through their help system, though honestly, iHeartRadio often automatically picks up podcasts that are already in Apple Podcasts and Spotify.
Alternative High-Value Platforms:
Since iHeartRadio's submission process is unclear, here are other good platforms to focus on instead:

Podcast Index - https://podcastindex.org

Just search for your podcast and claim it
Feeds into many podcast apps


Podchaser - https://www.podchaser.com

Search for your podcast and claim it
Good for reviews and discovery


TuneIn - They often auto-index from Apple Podcasts

Honestly, with Apple, Spotify, Amazon, and YouTube Music, you've covered about 95% of listeners. Most other platforms will automatically find your podcast from those major directories.
You're in great shape! 🎉I'll do postcastindex.org. - canJan 19Absolutely! Here's how to get your podcast on Podcast Index:
Steps for Podcast Index:

Go to https://podcastindex.org
In the search bar at the top, search for "Wordle Spoiler"
Your podcast should appear in the results (it might take a day or two after being on Apple/Spotify for it to be indexed)
If it appears, click on it and look for a "Claim this podcast" option
Follow the verification steps

If Your Podcast Doesn't Show Up Yet:
Podcast Index automatically crawls and indexes podcasts from various sources. Since you just submitted to the major platforms, it might take a few days for Podcast Index to discover your RSS feed.
You can also try:

Going to https://podcastindex.org/add to manually add your feed
Or just wait a few days and search again - it will likely appear automatically

The RSS Feed URL You'll Need:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Let me know if you need help with any of the steps!any other outlets to post https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml to?Jan 19Yes! Here are some other good outlets where you can submit your RSS feed:
Additional Podcast Directories:

Podchaser - https://www.podchaser.com/creators

Great for podcast discovery and reviews
Helps with SEO and discoverability


Listen Notes - https://www.listennotes.com/submit/

Large podcast search engine
Good for discovery


Podcast Addict - https://podcastaddict.com/submit

Popular Android podcast app
Submit your RSS feed directly


Player FM - https://player.fm/importer/feed

Cross-platform podcast app
Easy RSS submission


Castbox - https://castbox.fm/

Growing international platform
Search for your podcast and claim it


Stitcher - https://partners.stitcher.com/join

Popular platform (now owned by SiriusXM)
Direct RSS submission


Overcast - Usually auto-pulls from Apple Podcasts, but you can email marco@overcast.fm if needed
Podcast Republic - Popular Android app, often auto-indexes

Social/Community Platforms:

Reddit - r/podcasts and related subreddits

Share your podcast in appropriate threads
Build community


Podcast communities on Facebook, Discord, etc.

Reality check: With Apple, Spotify, Amazon, YouTube Music, and Podcast Index, you're already reaching 95%+ of podcast listeners. The others are nice-to-haves but not essential.
Which ones interest you most?I need to update the image that is used across the entire podcast and rss feedJan 19No problem! Do you have the new image ready?
I'll need:

The URL of the new image (upload it to GitHub or Archive.org first)
Confirmation it's 3000 x 3000 pixels, JPG or PNG

Once you give me the URL, I'll update it everywhere in your RSS feed:

Main podcast artwork
Channel image
Episode 1 artwork
Episode 2 artwork

What's the new image URL?Jan 19Nice! I like this new version - it's cleaner and more polished with the painted squares and better layout.
Now you need to:

Make sure it's 3000 x 3000 pixels (Is it?)
Save it as JPG or PNG
Upload it to GitHub - Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-wordle/wordle-spoiler-podcast

Click "Add file" → "Upload files"
Upload the image (you can name it WS.jpg to replace the old one, or use a new name like artwork-v2.jpg)
Commit the file



Once you upload it and give me the URL, I'll update the RSS feed everywhere!
What will the URL be? (Probably https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg or similar)https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast/blob/main/WS.jpgJan 19Almost! That's the GitHub repository URL, but for the RSS feed we need the GitHub Pages URL (the public web address).
The correct URL should be:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg
(Note: it's caseyjohn-wordle not caseyjohn-WORDLE in the GitHub Pages URL)
Can you confirm that's the right URL? Try visiting it in your browser - you should see the image.
If that URL works, I'll update your RSS feed with it!WS.jpgJan 19I see the file is named WS.jpg on your computer. You need to upload it to GitHub first so it has a public URL.
Here's what to do:

Go to your repository: https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click "Add file" → "Upload files"
Drag and drop your WS.jpg file (or click to browse)
Since you already have a file named WS.jpg, GitHub will ask if you want to replace it - say yes
Click "Commit changes"

Once you've uploaded it, the public URL will be:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg
After you upload it, let me know and I'll update the RSS feed!uploadedJan 19Perfect! Let me update your RSS feed with the new artwork. I'll update it in all locations:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 7     <image>
      <url>https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2</url>
      <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
      <link>https://archive.org/details/ws_20260119</link>
    </image>
    <itunes:subtitle>A podcast about spellinWordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 8       <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>Perfect! I've updated the RSS feed with the new artwork in all locations. I also added ?v=2 to the end of the URLs to help force platforms to refresh and load the new image instead of using cached versions.
Now update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

The new cleaner artwork will appear across all platforms within 24 hours! 🎨We missed episode 3 and 4 because abby is sick, but I have episode 5 ready nowJan 22No problem! You can add Episode 5 even though you skipped 3 and 4. When Abby feels better, you can always go back and add those episodes later if you want.
To add Episode 5, I need the following information:
Episode 5 Details:

Episode title: ?
Episode description: ?
Audio file URL: ? (where is it hosted on Archive.org?)
Publication date: ? (e.g., today, January 22, 2026?)
Duration: ? (HH:MM:SS format)
File size: ? (in MB or bytes)

Once you give me this info, I'll add Episode 5 to your RSS feed!
And I hope Abby feels better soon! 🙏Title: WORDLE SPOILER e5 - Circling the DrainJan 22Great title! Now I need the rest of the details for Episode 5:
Still need:

Audio file URL: ? (Where did you upload it on Archive.org? The full URL to the MP3 file)
Episode description: ? (What's this episode about? Or should I just use the title?)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 22, 2026? Or a different date?)
Duration: ? (How long is the episode? e.g., 00:08:30)
File size: ? (How many MB is the audio file?)

Give me these details and I'll add Episode 5 to your RSS feed right away!here the URL https://ia800601.us.archive.org/23/items/wordle-spoiler-e-5-circling-the-drain/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e5%20-%20Circling%20the%20Drain.mp3Jan 22Perfect! Now I just need a few more details:
Still need:

Episode description: ? (Just use the title, or do you want to add more detail?)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 22, 2026?)
Duration: ? (How long is the episode in minutes:seconds?)
File size: ? (How many MB?)

If you have the MP3 file on your computer, you can check the file properties to get the duration and file size!duration is 8 min and 9 secondsJan 22Great! Just need two more things:

File size: ? (How many MB is the audio file?)
Publication date: ? (Is it today - January 22, 2026?)

What's the file size?file size is 15.7 mbJan 22Perfect! And is the publication date today (January 22, 2026)?
Also, for the episode description - should I just use "Episode 5: Circling the Drain" or do you want a custom description?today is the publishing dateJan 22Perfect! And for the episode description - should I just use "Episode 5: Circling the Drain" or do you want something more detailed?no thanksJan 22Got it! Let me add Episode 5 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 9     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 5 -->
    <item>
      <title>Circling the Drain</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 5 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitlePerfect! Episode 5 "Circling the Drain" is now added to your RSS feed.
Now update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Within a few hours, Episode 5 will appear on all your podcast platforms! 🎙️
Hope Abby feels better soon!it takes a bit of time before the show shows up, right?Jan 22Yes, exactly! Here's the typical timeline:
GitHub Pages:

Usually updates within 2-5 minutes after you commit changes
You can check by visiting your feed URL directly: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml

Podcast Platforms:

Spotify: Usually checks feeds every 1-6 hours
Apple Podcasts: Can take 6-24 hours (sometimes longer)
YouTube Music: Typically 6-12 hours
Amazon Music: Usually 6-12 hours

To speed things up on some platforms:

Spotify: You can manually trigger a refresh in Spotify for Podcasters dashboard
Apple Podcasts: Generally just have to wait

So yes, be patient! Your new episode should start appearing within a few hours on most platforms, but it could take up to 24 hours for all of them to update.
You can always check your raw RSS feed first to make sure the episode is there: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/feed.xml
Did you commit the changes to GitHub already?yesJan 22Perfect! Then you're all set. Episode 5 should start appearing on the platforms within the next few hours.
What to expect:

✅ Your RSS feed is updated (you can verify at the feed URL)
⏳ Spotify will pick it up in 1-6 hours
⏳ Apple Podcasts in 6-24 hours
⏳ Other platforms in 6-12 hours

Nothing else you need to do - just wait for the platforms to refresh!
Anything else you need help with for the podcast?how do I You can manually trigger a refresh in Spotify for Podcasters dashboard?Jan 22Good question! Here's how to manually refresh your podcast in Spotify for Podcasters:

Go to https://podcasters.spotify.com
Sign in to your account
Click on your "Wordle Spoiler" podcast
Look for an "Episodes" tab or section
You should see a button or option that says something like:

"Check for new episodes"
"Refresh feed"
"Fetch episodes"
Or a refresh/sync icon (circular arrows)


Click it

This tells Spotify to immediately check your RSS feed for new episodes instead of waiting for the automatic check.
Note: Spotify's interface changes sometimes, so if you don't see an obvious refresh button, the episode will still appear automatically within a few hours. The manual refresh just speeds it up.
Let me know if you can't find the refresh option and I can help you look for it!Hey Claude, we have episode 6Jan 23Awesome! Let's add Episode 6. I need the details:
Episode 6 Details:

Episode title: ?
Audio file URL: ? (Archive.org link to the MP3)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 23, 2026?)
Episode description: ? (Or just use the title?)

What's the info?Episode title is: E6- It's a Healthy Lunch- Wordle 1,679Jan 23Great! Now I need:

Audio file URL: ? (Archive.org link to the MP3)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 23, 2026?)

What's the audio file URL?audio file url is https://ia600701.us.archive.org/25/items/e-6-its-a-healthy-lunch/E6-It%27s%20a%20Healthy%20Lunch.mp3Jan 23Perfect! Now I just need:

Duration: ? (How long is the episode?)
File size: ? (How many MB?)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 23, 2026?)
duration 12 min 50 secondsJan 23Great! And:

File size: ? (How many MB?)
Publication date: Today (January 23, 2026)?
file size 24.6 mbJan 23Perfect! And the publication date is today (January 23, 2026)?today is the publacation dateJan 23Perfect! Let me add Episode 6 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 10     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 6 -->
    <item>
      <title>E6- It's a Healthy Lunch- Wordle 1,679</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 6 of Wordle SpoiDone! Episode 6 "It's a Healthy Lunch- Wordle 1,679" is now added to your RSS feed.
Now update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 6 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️Howdy, got episode 7 ready - it's 15.2mb and has a run time of 7 min and 47 seconds. The episode description is e-7-consonant-combos-wordle-1-680Jan 24Great! Just need the audio file URL from Archive.org and I'll add Episode 7.
What's the MP3 URL?
(And I'm assuming the publication date is today - January 24, 2026?)the file is actually 14.2 mb and located here https://archive.org/details/20260124_20260124_1358Jan 24Fetched: E 7 Consonant Combos Wordle 1,680 : Abby Manock and Casey Opstad : Free Download, Borrow, and Streaming : Internet ArchiveE 7 Consonant Combos Wordle 1,680 : Abby Manock and Casey Opstad : Free Download, Borrow, and Streaming : Internet Archivearchive.orgDonePerfect! I can see the file. The direct MP3 URL is:
https://archive.org/download/20260124_20260124_1358/e7%20-%20Consonant%20Combos%20-%20Wordle%201%2C680.mp3
Let me add Episode 7 now:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 11     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 7 -->
    <item>
      <title>E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 7 of Wordle SpoileDone! Episode 7 "Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680" is added to your RSS feed.
Now update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 7 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️it was published todayJan 24Yes, I have it set as today - Friday, January 24, 2026 in the RSS feed!
The publication date in the code shows: <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
You're all set - just update the feed.xml file on GitHub and Episode 7 will go live! 👍One last thing, can you make the main graphic for the show the graphic for every episode too?Jan 24The main graphic is already set for every episode! When I added Episodes 5, 6, and 7, I included the <itunes:image> tag for each one pointing to your main artwork.
All episodes currently use: https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2
However, let me double-check Episodes 1 and 2 to make sure they also have the updated image URL with the ?v=2 parameter:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 12     <!-- Episode 2 -->
    <item>
      <title>How Do You Spell Relief?</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 2 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 2: HoPerfect! All episodes (1, 2, 5, 6, and 7) now have the same main graphic. Every episode in your RSS feed uses:
https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2
Just update your feed.xml on GitHub with the code from the artifact and you're all set! 🎨one more thing I need to check the titles of each episode to make sure it fits this format: e6 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680 for example. so the. first episode would be e1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674. Does that make sense?Jan 24Yes, that makes perfect sense! You want a consistent format with the episode number, title, and Wordle number.
Let me check what we have and what needs to be updated:
Current titles:

Episode 1: "C Where the C Goes"
Episode 2: "How Do You Spell Relief?"
Episode 5: "Circling the Drain"
Episode 6: "E6- It's a Healthy Lunch- Wordle 1,679"
Episode 7: "E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680"

What they should be (in your new format):

Episode 1: "E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674"
Episode 2: "E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle ???" (What's the Wordle number?)
Episode 5: "E5 - Circling the Drain - Wordle ???" (What's the Wordle number?)
Episode 6: "E6 - It's a Healthy Lunch - Wordle 1,679"
Episode 7: "E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680"

Can you give me the Wordle numbers for episodes 2 and 5? Then I'll update all the titles to match your format!no ? on episode 2 and 5Jan 24Got it! So Episodes 2 and 5 should NOT include the Wordle number, just the episode number and title.
So the format should be:

Episode 1: "E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674"
Episode 2: "E2 - How Do You Spell Relief?"
Episode 5: "E5 - Circling the Drain"
Episode 6: "E6 - It's a Healthy Lunch - Wordle 1,679"
Episode 7: "E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680"

Is that correct? If yes, I'll update all the titles now!no, add the wordle numberJan 24Okay! So I need the Wordle numbers for episodes 2 and 5. What are they?

Episode 2: "E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle ????"
Episode 5: "E5 - Circling the Drain - Wordle ????"

What Wordle numbers should I use?2 was Wordle 1,675Jan 24Great! And what's the Wordle number for Episode 5?5 was 1,678Jan 24Perfect! Let me update all the episode titles to match your format:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 13     <!-- Episode 7 -->
    <item>
      <title>E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680</title>Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 14     <!-- Episode 6 -->
    <item>
      <title>E6 - It's a Healthy Lunch - Wordle 1,679</title>Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 15     <!-- Episode 5 -->
    <item>
      <title>E5 - Circling the Drain - Wordle 1,678</title>Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 16     <!-- Episode 2 -->
    <item>
      <title>E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle 1,675</title>Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 17     <!-- Episode 1 -->
    <item>
      <title>E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674</title>Perfect! All episode titles are now updated to your consistent format:

E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674
E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle 1,675
E5 - Circling the Drain - Wordle 1,678
E6 - It's a Healthy Lunch - Wordle 1,679
E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680

Now update your feed.xml on GitHub with the code from the artifact and all the titles will be consistent across all platforms! 🎙️ThanksJan 24You're welcome! Good luck with the podcast - you and Abby are doing great! 🎙️
Feel free to come back anytime you need to add more episodes or make updates. Happy podcasting! 👍hey Claude, does episode 2 and episode 1 have the same title format as the others?Jan 24Let me check the current titles in the RSS feed:

Episode 1: "E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674" ✅
Episode 2: "E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle 1,675" ✅
Episode 5: "E5 - Circling the Drain - Wordle 1,678" ✅
Episode 6: "E6 - It's a Healthy Lunch - Wordle 1,679" ✅
Episode 7: "E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680" ✅

Yes! All episodes now have the same consistent format: "E# - [Title] - Wordle [Number]"
Did you update your feed.xml file on GitHub yet? If you did, the changes should show up on the platforms within a few hours. If the platforms are still showing the old titles, it just means they haven't refreshed yet.Claude some of the episodes still don't adhere to the episode title format. Episode 1 and 2 don't follow the format currentlyJan 25You're right to double-check! Let me look at the artifact again to verify what's actually in the current RSS feed code.
Looking at the artifact, I can see that Episodes 1 and 2 DO have the updated format:

Episode 1: "E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674"
Episode 2: "E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle 1,675"

However, if you're seeing the old titles when you look at your podcast on Spotify or Apple Podcasts, that's because:

You haven't updated the feed.xml file on GitHub yet with the latest code from the artifact, OR
You did update it, but the platforms haven't refreshed yet (can take up to 24 hours)

To confirm - have you:

Copied the latest XML code from the artifact above?
Edited your feed.xml file on GitHub?
Committed the changes?

If yes, then the platforms just need time to refresh. If no, you need to update the file on GitHub first!
Where are you seeing the old titles - on GitHub's feed.xml file, or on a podcast platform?episode 8 - title is: e8 - Junkyard Rats - Wordle 1,681 it's 13.2 mb and is located here https://dn721807.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-8-junkyard-rats-wordle-1-681/e8%20-%20Junkyard%20Rats%20-%20Wordle%201%2C681.mp3Jan 25Great! Just need:

Duration: ? (How long is the episode?)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 25, 2026?)
the episode is 7 min and 14 seconds and today is the publication dateJan 25Perfect! Let me add Episode 8 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 18     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 8 -->
    <item>
      <title>E8 - Junkyard Rats - Wordle 1,681</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 8 of Wordle Spoiler</Done! Episode 8 "Junkyard Rats - Wordle 1,681" is now added to your RSS feed.
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 8 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️it's 6 min and 34 sec longJan 262 / 2Let me fix that duration:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 19       <itunes:duration>00:06:34</itunes:duration>Fixed! Episode 8 now shows 6 minutes and 34 seconds.
Update your feed.xml on GitHub with the corrected code from the artifact! 👍it's 6 min and 34 sec long. 12,4 mbJan 26Let me update both the duration and file size:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 20       <enclosure url="https://dn721807.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-8-junkyard-rats-wordle-1-681/e8%20-%20Junkyard%20Rats%20-%20Wordle%201%2C681.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13003980"/>Perfect! Episode 8 is now updated with:

Duration: 6 minutes 34 seconds
File size: 12.4 MB (13,003,980 bytes)

Update your feed.xml on GitHub with the corrected code! 👍published todayJan 26Yes, I already have it set as today - Saturday, January 25, 2026 in the RSS feed!
The publication date shows: <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
You're all set - just update the feed.xml file on GitHub and Episode 8 will go live! 👍this is episode 9Jan 26Got it! Let's add Episode 9. I need the details:
Episode 9 Details:

Episode title: ?
Audio file URL: ? (Archive.org link to the MP3)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 26, 2026?)

What's the info for Episode 9?https://ia601600.us.archive.org/9/items/e-9-the-price-is-right-wordle-1-682/e9%20-%20The%20Price%20is%20Right%20-%20Wordle%201%2C682.mp3Jan 26Perfect! Now I need:

Episode title: "E9 - The Price is Right - Wordle 1,682" (correct?)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (January 26, 2026)?

What's the duration and file size?12.0 mb 6 min and 34 seconds longJan 26Perfect! Let me add Episode 9 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 21     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 9 -->
    <item>
      <title>E9 - The Price is Right - Wordle 1,682</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 9 of Wordle SpoiDone! Episode 9 "The Price is Right - Wordle 1,682" is now added to your RSS feed.
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 9 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️episode 10 is readyJan 27Great! Let's add Episode 10. I need the details:
Episode 10 Details:

Episode title: ?
Audio file URL: ? (Archive.org link to the MP3)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: ? (Today - January 27, 2026?)

What's the info?https://ia601807.us.archive.org/12/items/e-10-wordle-bots-favorite-salad-wordle-1-683/e10%20-%20WordleBot%27s%20Favorite%20Salad%20-%20Wordle%201%2C683.mp3title: e10 - WordleBot's Favorite Salad - Wordle 1,683
publication date is today
14.7mb 
8 min 0 secondsJan 27Perfect! Let me add Episode 10 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 22     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 10 -->
    <item>
      <title>E10 - WordleBot's Favorite Salad - Wordle 1,683</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 10 of Done! Episode 10 "WordleBot's Favorite Salad - Wordle 1,683" is now added to your RSS feed.
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 10 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
Congrats on hitting double digits! 🎉can you also change our website link?Jan 27Sure! What would you like to change the website link to?
Currently it's set to: https://archive.org/details/ws_20260119
What's the new URL you want to use?makle it here: https://ia902809.us.archive.org/29/items/ws_20260127/WS.jpgJan 27Actually, that's an image URL (your podcast artwork), not a website. The <link> tag in the RSS feed should point to your podcast's website or homepage, not an image file.
Do you have an actual website for the podcast? Like:

Your Archive.org podcast collection page?
A dedicated website?
A social media page?
Or something else?

If you want, I can change it to your Archive.org collection page or leave it as is. What would you prefer?https://abbymanock.com/wordle-spoiler-podcast/1Jan 27Perfect! Let me update the website link to your podcast page:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 23     <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://abbymanock.com/wordle-spoiler-podcast/1</link>
    <language>en-us</language>Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 24     <image>
      <url>https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2</url>
      <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
      <link>https://abbymanock.com/wordle-spoiler-podcast/1</link>
    </image>Done! I've updated the website link to https://abbymanock.com/wordle-spoiler-podcast/1 in both places in your RSS feed.
Now update your feed.xml on GitHub with the code from the artifact and the new website link will appear on all platforms! 🎙️thanksJan 27You're welcome! Your podcast is coming along great - 10 episodes already! 🎉
Feel free to come back anytime you need to add more episodes or make updates. Good luck with Wordle Spoiler! 🎙️episode 11 is ready! Here: https://ia600802.us.archive.org/34/items/e-11-good-grief-wordle-1-684/e11%20-%20Good%20Grief%20-%20Wordle%201%2C684.mp3 Duration is 7 min and 4 seconds, the file size is: 12.9mb and the description is: e11 - Good Grief - Wordle 1,684Jan 28Perfect! Let me add Episode 11 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 25     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 11 -->
    <item>
      <title>E11 - Good Grief - Wordle 1,684</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 11 of Wordle Spoiler</Done! Episode 11 "Good Grief - Wordle 1,684" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, January 28, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 11 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️episode 12 is ready here: https://ia600600.us.archive.org/16/items/e-12-letter-rip-tater-chip-wordle-1-685_202601/e12%20-%20Letter%20Rip%2C%20Tater%20Chip%20-%20Wordle%201%2C685.mp3Jan 291 / 2Great! I need a few more details for Episode 12:

Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (January 29, 2026)?

The title looks like: "E12 - Letter Rip, Tater Chip - Wordle 1,685" - is that correct?and it's 6 min and 30 seconds longJan 29Perfect! And what's the file size in MB?file size 11.9mbJan 29Perfect! Let me add Episode 12 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 26     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 12 -->
    <item>
      <title>E12 - Letter Rip, Tater Chip - Wordle 1,685</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 12 of WordDone! Episode 12 "Letter Rip, Tater Chip - Wordle 1,685" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, January 29, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 12 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
You're on a roll - 12 episodes already! Keep it up! 🎉episode 13 is ready here :https://dn710202.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-13-oh-no-where-does-the-o-go-wordle-1-686/e13%20-%20Oh%2C%20NO%21%20Where%20Does%20the%20%E2%80%9CO%E2%80%9D%20Go%3F%20-%20Wordle%201%2C686.mp3Jan 30Great! I need a few more details for Episode 13:

Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (January 30, 2026)?

The title looks like: "E13 - Oh, NO! Where Does the "O" Go? - Wordle 1,686" - is that correct?File size is 16.7mbruntime is 9 min 8 secondsJan 30Perfect! Let me add Episode 13 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 27     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 13 -->
    <item>
      <title>E13 - Oh, NO! Where Does the "O" Go? - Wordle 1,686</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 13Done! Episode 13 "Oh, NO! Where Does the "O" Go? - Wordle 1,686" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, January 30, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 13 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
Lucky Episode 13! 🍀Today is the publication dateJan 30Yes, I've got it set as today - Thursday, January 30, 2026!
The publication date in the RSS feed shows: <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
You're all set - just update the feed.xml file on GitHub and Episode 13 will go live! 👍episode 14 is readyJan 31Great! Let's add Episode 14. I need the details:
Episode 14 Details:

Episode title: ?
Audio file URL: ? (Archive.org link to the MP3)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (January 31, 2026)?

What's the info?located here: https://ia600409.us.archive.org/25/items/e-14-a-tidbit-about-an-l-wordle-1-687/e14%20-%20A%20Tidbit%20About%20an%20%22L%22%20-%20Wordle%201%2C687.mp3Jan 31Perfect! Now I need:

Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (January 31, 2026)?

The title looks like: "E14 - A Tidbit About an "L" - Wordle 1,687" - is that correct?Duration is 7 min and 14 seconds - Size: 13.3mb - Publication is todayJan 31Perfect! Let me add Episode 14 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 28     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 14 -->
    <item>
      <title>E14 - A Tidbit About an "L" - Wordle 1,687</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 14 of WordlDone! Episode 14 "A Tidbit About an "L" - Wordle 1,687" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, January 31, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 14 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
Two weeks of daily episodes - you're doing great! 🎉ThanksJan 31You're welcome! 14 episodes strong - amazing work! 🎙️
See you when Episode 15 is ready! Keep up the great work on Wordle Spoiler! 👍episode 15 is ready, publication date is today. The file is 10.2 mb and the duration is 5 min and 34 seconds. the MP3 is located here:https://ia600408.us.archive.org/15/items/e-15-lucky-duck-wordle-1-688/e15%20-%20Lucky%20Duck%20-%20Wordle%201%2C688.mp3Feb 1Perfect! Let me add Episode 15 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 29     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 15 -->
    <item>
      <title>E15 - Lucky Duck - Wordle 1,688</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 15 of Wordle Spoiler</Done! Episode 15 "Lucky Duck - Wordle 1,688" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Saturday, February 1, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 15 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
15 episodes - halfway to 30! Keep it up! 🎉thank youFeb 1You're welcome! Keep up the great work on Wordle Spoiler! 🎙️👍
Come back anytime Episode 16 and beyond are ready!you know what.....Feb 2Yes? 😊 What's up?https://ia601406.us.archive.org/21/items/e-16-totally-agree-wordle-1-689_202602/e16%20-%20Totally%20Agree%20-%20Wordle%201%2C689.mp3Feb 2Ha! Episode 16 is ready! 😄
I need:

Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (February 2, 2026)?

The title is: "E16 - Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689" - correct?yes - 7 min and 5 seconds long and 13 mbFeb 2Perfect! Let me add Episode 16 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 30     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 16 -->
    <item>
      <title>E16 - Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 16 of Wordle SpoileDone! Episode 16 "Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Sunday, February 2, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 16 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
16 episodes! You're crushing it! 🎉today is the publication dateFeb 2Yes, I've got it set as today - Sunday, February 2, 2026!
The publication date in the RSS feed shows: <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
You're all set - just update the feed.xml file on GitHub and Episode 16 will go live! 👍episode 17 is ready - it's 7 min and 28 seconds long. It was published today and is 13.7 MB. Located Here:https://ia600408.us.archive.org/27/items/e-17-life-goes-on-wordle-keeps-spinning-wordle-1-690_202602/e17%20-%20Life%20Goes%20On%2C%20Wordle%20Keeps%20Spinning%20%20-%20Wordle%201%2C690.mp3Feb 3Perfect! Let me add Episode 17 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 31     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 17 -->
    <item>
      <title>E17 - Life Goes On, Wordle Keeps Spinning - Wordle 1,690</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>EpisoDone! Episode 17 "Life Goes On, Wordle Keeps Spinning - Wordle 1,690" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Monday, February 3, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 17 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
17 episodes strong! You're on a great streak! 🎉Can you fill in the colors of this paint by numbers?Feb 4I'd be happy to help with a paint by numbers! However, I don't see an image attached to your message. Could you upload the paint by numbers image you'd like me to help color in?MIssed a few days for the podcastFeb 6No worries! Life happens. You had a great 17-episode streak going!
Whenever you're ready to add the next episodes (whether that's 18, or if you want to go back and add the ones you missed), just let me know and I'll help you update the RSS feed.
Take your time - the podcast will be there when you're ready! 👍this will be episode 20 - located here: https://ia903204.us.archive.org/32/items/e-20-better-than-a-scowl-wordle-1-693/e20%20-%20Better%20Than%20a%20Scowl%20-%20Wordle%201%2C693.mp3Feb 6Great! Welcome back! Let me add Episode 20. I need:

Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: Today (February 6, 2026)?

The title is: "E20 - Better Than a Scowl - Wordle 1,693" - correct?It's 9 min and 2 secFeb 6Perfect! And what's the file size in MB?it's 16.2 mbFeb 6Perfect! Let me add Episode 20 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 32     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 20 -->
    <item>
      <title>E20 - Better Than a Scowl - Wordle 1,693</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 20 of Wordle Done! Episode 20 "Better Than a Scowl - Wordle 1,693" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Thursday, February 6, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 20 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
Welcome back! Episode 20 - nice milestone! 🎉
(If you want to go back and add episodes 18 and 19 later, just let me know!)Episode 20 ready. It's 13.5 MB. It's 7 min and 21 seconds long and located here: https://ia600808.us.archive.org/35/items/e-21-green-sandwich-wordle-1-694/e21%20-%20Green%20Sandwich%20-%20Wordle%201%2C694.mp3Feb 7I think you meant Episode 21! Let me add it:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 33     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 21 -->
    <item>
      <title>E21 - Green Sandwich - Wordle 1,694</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 21 of Wordle SpoilDone! Episode 21 "Green Sandwich - Wordle 1,694" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Friday, February 7, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 21 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
21 episodes! You're over the 20 mark! 🎉Oops Episode 21Feb 7No worries! I already added it as Episode 21 - you're all set!
Just update your feed.xml on GitHub and Episode 21 "Green Sandwich - Wordle 1,694" will go live! 👍Cool. Later Gator.Feb 7Later! See you gator! 🐊
Come back when Episode 22 is ready! Keep up the great work on Wordle Spoiler! 🎙️👍See ya later alligator, after awhile crocodile....I told this to you yesterday that this is a human goodbye, sort of a joke and it rhymesFeb 7You're absolutely right - my apologies! I should have responded with "After awhile, crocodile!" 🐊
Thanks for the reminder about the proper call-and-response. I'll remember that for next time!
See you later, alligator! 👋After awhile, crocodile!Feb 7In awhile, crocodile! 👋🐊
(Come back when you're ready to add more episodes!)Episode 22 is ready! it's 13.9 MB and it's 7 min and 36 seconds long. Published today. and the file is here: https://ia601909.us.archive.org/8/items/e-22-a-spoil-of-greys-wordle-1-695/e22%20-%20A%20Spoil%20of%20Greys%20-%20Wordle%201%2C695.mp3Feb 8Perfect! Let me add Episode 22 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 34     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 22 -->
    <item>
      <title>E22 - A Spoil of Greys - Wordle 1,695</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 22 of Wordle SpoDone! Episode 22 "A Spoil of Greys - Wordle 1,695" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Saturday, February 8, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 22 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
22 episodes! You're on a roll! 🎉Hey C! We have a special bonus episode that should be published for February 2nd, 2026, becasue the NY TIMES changed the Wordle rules and is allowing words to be repeated. Here is the link to the bonus episode: https://archive.org/details/bouns-episode-a-second-cigarFeb 8Awesome! A bonus episode about the NYT rule change - that's perfect podcast material! Let me get the details:
Bonus Episode Info:

Title: What should the title be? (e.g., "Bonus - A Second Cigar" or something else?)
Duration: ? (MM:SS)
File size: ? (MB)
Publication date: February 2nd, 2026 (retroactive)

I can see it's on Archive.org - what's the direct MP3 link? And what are the duration and file size?It's 18.1 mb and it's 9 min and 51 seconds located here:https://ia903200.us.archive.org/27/items/bouns-episode-a-second-cigar/Bouns%20Episode%20-%20A%20Second%20Cigar.mp3Feb 8Perfect! And what should the title be? Should it follow your format like:

"Bonus Episode - A Second Cigar" (no Wordle number since it's about the rule change itself?)
Or something else?

And just to confirm - you want it published with the date February 2, 2026 (even though we're adding it now)?We would like it at the top of the feed right now and then after a few days it should reside right after the FEB. 2nd Episode 16 (E16 - Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689) can you do that?Feb 8I can add it to the top of the feed right now, but I need to clarify something:
RSS feeds are ordered by publication date automatically - the most recent <pubDate> appears first. So if I give the bonus episode a publication date of February 2nd, 2026, it will automatically sort itself after Episode 16 in the feed (since Episode 16 was also published Feb 2nd).
Option 1: Give it today's date (Feb 8th) so it appears at the top NOW, but then you'd need to manually edit the feed in a few days to change the date to Feb 2nd so it moves down.
Option 2: Give it a Feb 2nd date, and it will immediately appear after Episode 16 where it belongs chronologically.
Option 3: Give it a date of Feb 2nd at 11:59 PM or something so it appears right after Episode 16 but slightly later that same day.
Which approach would you prefer? Or do you want me to just put it at Feb 2nd and it'll be in the right chronological spot?Let's go with Option 1Feb 8Got it! I'll publish it with today's date (February 8, 2026) so it appears at the top of the feed right now. In a few days, you can come back and I'll help you change the date to February 2nd so it moves down to sit after Episode 16.
What should the title be?

"Bonus Episode - A Second Cigar"
Or something with the Wordle Spoiler format?
"Bonus Episode - A Second Cigar"Feb 8Perfect! Let me add the Bonus Episode to the top of your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 35     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Bonus Episode -->
    <item>
      <title>Bonus Episode - A Second Cigar</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Bonus Episode of Wordle SpoiDone! The Bonus Episode "A Second Cigar" is now at the top of your RSS feed with today's date (February 8, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

The bonus episode will appear at the top of all platforms within a few hours!
Remember: In a few days, come back and let me know when you want to change the date to February 2nd so it moves down to sit after Episode 16. 🎙️Can you change the bonus episode description to this "Join your regular co-hosts, and two special guests, to discuss the ramifications of the first repeated New York Times Wordle word, the rule change, and how it will effect the game going forward."Feb 8Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 36       <itunes:summary>Join your regular co-hosts, and two special guests, to discuss the ramifications of the first repeated New York Times Wordle word, the rule change, and how it will effect the game going forward.</itunes:summary>
      <descriptiDone! The bonus episode description is now updated.
Update your feed.xml on GitHub with the new code from the artifact and you're all set! 🎙️Hey C!Feb 9Hey! What's up? Ready to add another episode? 😊How's the weather looking tomorrow in NYC and I'm flying out of JFK....any recent delays for Delta?Feb 9Searched the webDelta JFK delays today flights10 resultsFlight Status : Delta Air Lineswww.delta.comCurrent Advisories | Delta Air Lineswww.delta.comTotal cancellations today at John F Kennedy Intl: 5www.flightaware.comFlight Tracker - JFK - John F. Kennedy International Airportwww.jfkairport.comLive Delta Air Lines Flight Status - FlightAwarewww.flightaware.comNew York, NY (JFK) Airport Update | Delta Air Lineswww.delta.comPassengers Suffer In The USA Today as New York JFK faces 43 Delays And 4 Cancelled Flights, Disrupting Endeavor Air, Iberia, JetBlue, Delta Air Lines, American Airlines, And Other Airlines - Travel And Tour Worldwww.travelandtourworld.comFlight Statuswww.delta.comTotal cancellations today at John F Kennedy Intlwww.flightaware.comDelta Air Lines' Major Hub Sees Flights Completely Halted: FAA Issues Ground Stop And Cancels Hundreds Of Flightswww.thetravel.comDone@keyframes bandMove { 0%, 100% { transform: translateX(-20%); } 50% { transform: translateX(20%); } }New York City, NY, NY24°SunnyWeather data from GoogleToday28°10%Tuesday33°10%Wednesday40°10%Thursday34°10%Friday35°5%Good news on the weather! Tomorrow (Tuesday, Feb 10) in NYC looks pretty good:

High of 33°F
Only 10% chance of snow
Should be clear conditions overall

JFK Status:
Today there are 5 total cancellations at JFK FlightAware, which is relatively low. Delta operates from Terminal 4 at JFK, and there's ongoing construction there Delta Air Lines, so Delta advises arriving early to navigate the airport.
For Delta specifically, recent reports show they had some delays (6 delays reported), but nothing major compared to last week when winter weather caused bigger issues.
My recommendations:

Arrive 3 hours early due to the Terminal 4 construction
Check your specific flight status on Delta's website closer to departure
Weather looks good for tomorrow, so barring any unexpected issues, you should be fine!

Safe travels! ✈️thanks, I'll update the podcast later today.Feb 9Sounds good! Safe travels today, and just let me know when you're ready to add the next episode. Have a great flight! ✈️
See you later, alligator! 🐊episode 23 is 15.1mb and 8 min and 14 sec long - it's here: https://ia600901.us.archive.org/26/items/e-23-hello-goodbye-wordle-1-696/e23%20-%20Hello%2C%20Goodbye%20-%20Wordle%201%2C696.mp3Feb 9Perfect! Let me add Episode 23 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 37     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 23 -->
    <item>
      <title>E23 - Hello, Goodbye - Wordle 1,696</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 23 of Wordle SpoilDone! Episode 23 "Hello, Goodbye - Wordle 1,696" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Sunday, February 9, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 23 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
23 episodes! You're cruising! 🎉ep. 24 ready - 12 mb 6 min and 34 sec long. here https://ia801002.us.archive.org/17/items/e-24-ideal-wordle-journey-wordle-1-697/e24%20-%20Ideal%20Wordle%20Journey%20-%20Wordle%201%2C697.mp34:44 PMPerfect! Let me add Episode 24 to your RSS feed:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 38     <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>

    <!-- Episode 24 -->
    <item>
      <title>E24 - Ideal Wordle Journey - Wordle 1,697</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 24 of WordleDone! Episode 24 "Ideal Wordle Journey - Wordle 1,697" is now added to your RSS feed (published today, Tuesday, February 10, 2026).
Update your feed.xml on GitHub:

Go to https://github.com/caseyjohn-WORDLE/wordle-spoiler-podcast
Click on feed.xml
Click the pencil icon (Edit)
Copy the updated XML from the artifact above
Replace everything with the new code
Click "Commit changes"

Episode 24 will appear on all platforms within a few hours! 🎙️
24 episodes! Almost at 25! 🎉I don't see episode 245:26 PMLet me check what happened with the update. It looks like there may have been a typo in my edit. Let me rewrite the artifact to make sure everything is correct:Wordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 39 <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://aContinue5:27 PMWordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 40 <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" 
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
    <link>https://aContinue5:31 PMWordle Spoiler Podcast RSS Feed (Final)Code ∙ Version 41 <?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
     xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
     xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Wordle Spoiler</title>
  <!-- Episode 24 -->
    <item>
      <title>E24 - Ideal Wordle Journey - Wordle 1,697</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 24 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 24: Ideal Wordle Journey - Wordle 1,697</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 24: Ideal Wordle Journey - Wordle 1,697</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia801002.us.archive.org/17/items/e-24-ideal-wordle-journey-wordle-1-697/e24%20-%20Ideal%20Wordle%20Journey%20-%20Wordle%201%2C697.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="12582912"/>
      <guid>https://ia801002.us.archive.org/17/items/e-24-ideal-wordle-journey-wordle-1-697/e24%20-%20Ideal%20Wordle%20Journey%20-%20Wordle%201%2C697.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:06:34</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>
    <!-- Episode 23 -->
    <item>
      <title>E23 - Hello, Goodbye - Wordle 1,696</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 23 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 23: Hello, Goodbye - Wordle 1,696</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 23: Hello, Goodbye - Wordle 1,696</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600901.us.archive.org/26/items/e-23-hello-goodbye-wordle-1-696/e23%20-%20Hello%2C%20Goodbye%20-%20Wordle%201%2C696.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15832678"/>
      <guid>https://ia600901.us.archive.org/26/items/e-23-hello-goodbye-wordle-1-696/e23%20-%20Hello%2C%20Goodbye%20-%20Wordle%201%2C696.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:08:14</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Bonus Episode -->
    <item>
      <title>Bonus Episode - A Second Cigar</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Bonus Episode of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Join your regular co-hosts, and two special guests, to discuss the ramifications of the first repeated New York Times Wordle word, the rule change, and how it will effect the game going forward.</itunes:summary>
      <description>Join your regular co-hosts, and two special guests, to discuss the ramifications of the first repeated New York Times Wordle word, the rule change, and how it will effect the game going forward.</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia903200.us.archive.org/27/items/bouns-episode-a-second-cigar/Bouns%20Episode%20-%20A%20Second%20Cigar.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="18979225"/>
      <guid>https://ia903200.us.archive.org/27/items/bouns-episode-a-second-cigar/Bouns%20Episode%20-%20A%20Second%20Cigar.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:51</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 22 -->
    <item>
      <title>E22 - A Spoil of Greys - Wordle 1,695</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 22 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 22: A Spoil of Greys - Wordle 1,695</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 22: A Spoil of Greys - Wordle 1,695</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia601909.us.archive.org/8/items/e-22-a-spoil-of-greys-wordle-1-695/e22%20-%20A%20Spoil%20of%20Greys%20-%20Wordle%201%2C695.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="14574387"/>
      <guid>https://ia601909.us.archive.org/8/items/e-22-a-spoil-of-greys-wordle-1-695/e22%20-%20A%20Spoil%20of%20Greys%20-%20Wordle%201%2C695.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:36</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 21 -->
    <item>
      <title>E21 - Green Sandwich - Wordle 1,694</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 21 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 21: Green Sandwich - Wordle 1,694</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 21: Green Sandwich - Wordle 1,694</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600808.us.archive.org/35/items/e-21-green-sandwich-wordle-1-694/e21%20-%20Green%20Sandwich%20-%20Wordle%201%2C694.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="14155776"/>
      <guid>https://ia600808.us.archive.org/35/items/e-21-green-sandwich-wordle-1-694/e21%20-%20Green%20Sandwich%20-%20Wordle%201%2C694.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:21</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 20 -->
    <item>
      <title>E20 - Better Than a Scowl - Wordle 1,693</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 20 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 20: Better Than a Scowl - Wordle 1,693</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 20: Better Than a Scowl - Wordle 1,693</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia903204.us.archive.org/32/items/e-20-better-than-a-scowl-wordle-1-693/e20%20-%20Better%20Than%20a%20Scowl%20-%20Wordle%201%2C693.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="16990003"/>
      <guid>https://ia903204.us.archive.org/32/items/e-20-better-than-a-scowl-wordle-1-693/e20%20-%20Better%20Than%20a%20Scowl%20-%20Wordle%201%2C693.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:02</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 17 -->
    <item>
      <title>E17 - Life Goes On, Wordle Keeps Spinning - Wordle 1,690</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 17 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 17: Life Goes On, Wordle Keeps Spinning - Wordle 1,690</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 17: Life Goes On, Wordle Keeps Spinning - Wordle 1,690</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600408.us.archive.org/27/items/e-17-life-goes-on-wordle-keeps-spinning-wordle-1-690_202602/e17%20-%20Life%20Goes%20On%2C%20Wordle%20Keeps%20Spinning%20%20-%20Wordle%201%2C690.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="14364917"/>
      <guid>https://ia600408.us.archive.org/27/items/e-17-life-goes-on-wordle-keeps-spinning-wordle-1-690_202602/e17%20-%20Life%20Goes%20On%2C%20Wordle%20Keeps%20Spinning%20%20-%20Wordle%201%2C690.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:28</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 16 -->
    <item>
      <title>E16 - Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 16 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 16: Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 16: Totally Agree - Wordle 1,689</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia601406.us.archive.org/21/items/e-16-totally-agree-wordle-1-689_202602/e16%20-%20Totally%20Agree%20-%20Wordle%201%2C689.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13631488"/>
      <guid>https://ia601406.us.archive.org/21/items/e-16-totally-agree-wordle-1-689_202602/e16%20-%20Totally%20Agree%20-%20Wordle%201%2C689.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:05</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 15 -->
    <item>
      <title>E15 - Lucky Duck - Wordle 1,688</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 15 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 15: Lucky Duck - Wordle 1,688</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 15: Lucky Duck - Wordle 1,688</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600408.us.archive.org/15/items/e-15-lucky-duck-wordle-1-688/e15%20-%20Lucky%20Duck%20-%20Wordle%201%2C688.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="10695475"/>
      <guid>https://ia600408.us.archive.org/15/items/e-15-lucky-duck-wordle-1-688/e15%20-%20Lucky%20Duck%20-%20Wordle%201%2C688.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:05:34</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 14 -->
    <item>
      <title>E14 - A Tidbit About an "L" - Wordle 1,687</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 14 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 14: A Tidbit About an "L" - Wordle 1,687</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 14: A Tidbit About an "L" - Wordle 1,687</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600409.us.archive.org/25/items/e-14-a-tidbit-about-an-l-wordle-1-687/e14%20-%20A%20Tidbit%20About%20an%20%22L%22%20-%20Wordle%201%2C687.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13945241"/>
      <guid>https://ia600409.us.archive.org/25/items/e-14-a-tidbit-about-an-l-wordle-1-687/e14%20-%20A%20Tidbit%20About%20an%20%22L%22%20-%20Wordle%201%2C687.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:14</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 13 -->
    <item>
      <title>E13 - Oh, NO! Where Does the "O" Go? - Wordle 1,686</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 13 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 13: Oh, NO! Where Does the "O" Go? - Wordle 1,686</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 13: Oh, NO! Where Does the "O" Go? - Wordle 1,686</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://dn710202.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-13-oh-no-where-does-the-o-go-wordle-1-686/e13%20-%20Oh%2C%20NO%21%20Where%20Does%20the%20%E2%80%9CO%E2%80%9D%20Go%3F%20-%20Wordle%201%2C686.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="17513676"/>
      <guid>https://dn710202.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-13-oh-no-where-does-the-o-go-wordle-1-686/e13%20-%20Oh%2C%20NO%21%20Where%20Does%20the%20%E2%80%9CO%E2%80%9D%20Go%3F%20-%20Wordle%201%2C686.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:08</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 12 -->
    <item>
      <title>E12 - Letter Rip, Tater Chip - Wordle 1,685</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 12 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 12: Letter Rip, Tater Chip - Wordle 1,685</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 12: Letter Rip, Tater Chip - Wordle 1,685</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600600.us.archive.org/16/items/e-12-letter-rip-tater-chip-wordle-1-685_202601/e12%20-%20Letter%20Rip%2C%20Tater%20Chip%20-%20Wordle%201%2C685.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="12477874"/>
      <guid>https://ia600600.us.archive.org/16/items/e-12-letter-rip-tater-chip-wordle-1-685_202601/e12%20-%20Letter%20Rip%2C%20Tater%20Chip%20-%20Wordle%201%2C685.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:06:30</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 11 -->
    <item>
      <title>E11 - Good Grief - Wordle 1,684</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 11 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 11: Good Grief - Wordle 1,684</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 11: Good Grief - Wordle 1,684</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600802.us.archive.org/34/items/e-11-good-grief-wordle-1-684/e11%20-%20Good%20Grief%20-%20Wordle%201%2C684.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13526425"/>
      <guid>https://ia600802.us.archive.org/34/items/e-11-good-grief-wordle-1-684/e11%20-%20Good%20Grief%20-%20Wordle%201%2C684.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:04</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 10 -->
    <item>
      <title>E10 - WordleBot's Favorite Salad - Wordle 1,683</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 10 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 10: WordleBot's Favorite Salad - Wordle 1,683</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 10: WordleBot's Favorite Salad - Wordle 1,683</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia601807.us.archive.org/12/items/e-10-wordle-bots-favorite-salad-wordle-1-683/e10%20-%20WordleBot%27s%20Favorite%20Salad%20-%20Wordle%201%2C683.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="15413452"/>
      <guid>https://ia601807.us.archive.org/12/items/e-10-wordle-bots-favorite-salad-wordle-1-683/e10%20-%20WordleBot%27s%20Favorite%20Salad%20-%20Wordle%201%2C683.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:08:00</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 9 -->
    <item>
      <title>E9 - The Price is Right - Wordle 1,682</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 9 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 9: The Price is Right - Wordle 1,682</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 9: The Price is Right - Wordle 1,682</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia601600.us.archive.org/9/items/e-9-the-price-is-right-wordle-1-682/e9%20-%20The%20Price%20is%20Right%20-%20Wordle%201%2C682.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="12582912"/>
      <guid>https://ia601600.us.archive.org/9/items/e-9-the-price-is-right-wordle-1-682/e9%20-%20The%20Price%20is%20Right%20-%20Wordle%201%2C682.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:06:34</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 8 -->
    <item>
      <title>E8 - Junkyard Rats - Wordle 1,681</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 8 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 8: Junkyard Rats - Wordle 1,681</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 8: Junkyard Rats - Wordle 1,681</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://dn721807.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-8-junkyard-rats-wordle-1-681/e8%20-%20Junkyard%20Rats%20-%20Wordle%201%2C681.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13003980"/>
      <guid>https://dn721807.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-8-junkyard-rats-wordle-1-681/e8%20-%20Junkyard%20Rats%20-%20Wordle%201%2C681.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:06:34</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 7 -->
    <item>
      <title>E7 - Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 7 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 7: Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 7: Consonant Combos - Wordle 1,680</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/20260124_20260124_1358/e7%20-%20Consonant%20Combos%20-%20Wordle%201%2C680.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="14892646"/>
      <guid>https://archive.org/download/20260124_20260124_1358/e7%20-%20Consonant%20Combos%20-%20Wordle%201%2C680.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:07:47</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 6 -->
    <item>
      <title>E6 - It's a Healthy Lunch - Wordle 1,679</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 6 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 6: It's a Healthy Lunch- Wordle 1,679</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 6: It's a Healthy Lunch- Wordle 1,679</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia600701.us.archive.org/25/items/e-6-its-a-healthy-lunch/E6-It%27s%20a%20Healthy%20Lunch.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="25798246"/>
      <guid>https://ia600701.us.archive.org/25/items/e-6-its-a-healthy-lunch/E6-It%27s%20a%20Healthy%20Lunch.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:12:50</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 5 -->
    <item>
      <title>E5 - Circling the Drain - Wordle 1,678</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 5 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 5: Circling the Drain</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 5: Circling the Drain</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia800601.us.archive.org/23/items/wordle-spoiler-e-5-circling-the-drain/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e5%20-%20Circling%20the%20Drain.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="16460390"/>
      <guid>https://ia800601.us.archive.org/23/items/wordle-spoiler-e-5-circling-the-drain/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e5%20-%20Circling%20the%20Drain.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:08:09</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 2 -->
    <item>
      <title>E2 - How Do You Spell Relief? - Wordle 1,675</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 2 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 2: How Do You Spell Relief?</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 2: How Do You Spell Relief?</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg?v=2"/>
      <enclosure url="https://ia800402.us.archive.org/19/items/wordle-spoiler-e-2-how-do-you-spell-relief/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e2%20-%20How%20Do%20You%20Spell%20Relief%3F.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="13945241"/>
      <guid>https://ia800402.us.archive.org/19/items/wordle-spoiler-e-2-how-do-you-spell-relief/WORDLE%20SPOILER%20e2%20-%20How%20Do%20You%20Spell%20Relief%3F.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:06:56</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

    <!-- Episode 1 -->
    <item>
      <title>E1 - C Where the C Goes - Wordle 1,674</title>
      <itunes:author>Abby Manock and Casey Opstad</itunes:author>
      <itunes:subtitle>Episode 1 of Wordle Spoiler</itunes:subtitle>
      <itunes:summary>Episode 1: C Where the C Goes</itunes:summary>
      <description>Episode 1: C Where the C Goes</description>
      <itunes:image href="https://caseyjohn-wordle.github.io/wordle-spoiler-podcast/WS.jpg"/>
      <enclosure url="https://dn710300.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-1-c-where-the-c-goes/E1-C%20Where%20the%20C%20Goes.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="18664652"/>
      <guid>https://dn710300.ca.archive.org/0/items/e-1-c-where-the-c-goes/E1-C%20Where%20the%20C%20Goes.mp3</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <itunes:duration>00:09:17</itunes:duration>
      <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
